t-shirtforums.com 2018-05-15

# T-Shirt Forums Privacy Policy

**How this site handles your personal information**

**We know that you value your privacy. Your privacy is important to us, too.**

Your privacy is important to **T-ShirtForums.com**. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

Each time you use this website, the current version of this policy will apply. Policy changes will be reflected on this page. Since users are required to accept all changes to this policy in our [Terms of Use Agreement](http://www.t-shirtforums.com/view_tos.htm) , we encourage you to regularly check the date of this policy and review any changes made since the last time you used the site.   

**1\. This site collects information that users voluntarily provide through its registration forms, surveys, and contest entry forms**

Our site contains forms that require a user to give us valid and accurate contact information (like your name and email address during registration, and postal address in the case of a contest or giveaway).

Contact information from the registration form is used to send information to users about our website. We use the information you submit to fulfill your requests, provide site functionality, improve site quality, personalize your experience, display relevant advertising, provide customer support, message you, back up our systems, allow for disaster recovery, and comply with legal obligations.

A user’s contact information from surveys and contests is also used to get in touch with the user when necessary. Demographic and profile data is used to tailor our user’s experience on our website, by showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

**2\. Users submit certain information automatically simply by viewing the website**

We use information our site collects, such as your IP address, to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information in order to tailor our website to better suit your needs. 

**3\. This site uses cookies to enhance the user's experience**

Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Some of our merchant partners (PayPal) may also use cookies for similar purposes. You can learn more about our merchant partners’ policies by visiting their websites. 

**4\. This site serves third-party advertising**

Our site serves ads by our own advertising software as well as third party ads. We may use an outside ad company, such as Google, to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

Google and Advertising:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on their visit to our site and other sites on the internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by [visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**5\. We use the data we collect from users in a variety of ways**

Although we may use user information in any way not specifically limited by the Terms of Use and this privacy policy, it is useful to understand how we typically use the information we collect from users.

  * To improve the website
  * To personalize your experience
  * To process transactions
  * To facilitate contests and surveys

We may also disclose and transfer your personal information to any successors-in-interest in the event that T-Shirt Forums is acquired by, sold to, merged with, or transferred to a third party. Some or all of your personal information provided to T-Shirt Forums could be amongst the assets transferred.

**6\. External sites that this website links to are not subject to this policy**

This site contains links to other sites. T-ShirtForums.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**7\. Private messages are not necessarily completely "private"**

The purpose of private messaging is to allow for discreet conversations to take place between members. Although private messages are normally only accessible by those who send and receive them, they are part of the database and as such, property of The T-ShirtForums.com. An Administrator could theoretically locate the Private Messages in the database and read them, for example, to investigate a wrongdoing as required by law enforcement. Private messages are private, but not necessarily secret.

**8\. This site's transactions are not handled internally**

T-ShirtForums.com uses an outside online payment service to provide secure online transactions to our members so that they can make payments online with the security and confidence they deserve. We have chosen to form a relationship with PayPal, the online leader for such secure online payment services because they are as dedicated to your privacy and security as we are. If you have any questions about PayPal.com's policies regarding these issues, feel free to visit their website at: [https://www.paypal.com](https://www.paypal.com/).

**9\. Although your data is reasonably secure, no security measures are 100% secure**

No method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. The security measures that are in place include partnering with a secure online payment service such as PayPal.com and keeping all email on a separate computer so that your information is not shared with anyone. 

**10\. Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us.

  1. You can [click to email us.](http://www.t-shirtforums.com/sendmessage.php)

**11\. Users have the ability to change/modify their previously provided information**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

  1. You can login to your account at: <http://www.t-shirtforums.com/login.php>
  2. After you login, you can change your email address on file here: <http://www.t-shirtforums.com/profile.php?do=editpassword>

**Data Retention and Account Termination**

We may keep your data as long as is permitted or required under the law. If you terminate your account, we can remove your username from the site, but may retain your data in our system to satisfy any of the authorized uses under this privacy policy. 

For example, we may use retained data to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the site or to comply with legal obligations. Please note that information may exist in backup storage even after it has been removed from our active databases.  

**We Do Not Collect Personal Information From Children**

This website complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) and is not intended for children under 18 years of age. This website does not knowingly or intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from or market to individuals under the age of 18. 

If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us [here](http://www.t-shirtforums.com/sendmessage.php). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact: 

Rodney Blackwell  
T-ShirtForums.com  
3104 O Street, Suite 316  
Sacramento, CA 95816   
USA

 **Email:  **[click here to email us](http://www.t-shirtforums.com/sendmessage.php)  
 **Fax:** (916) 405-3405   
 **Phone:** (916) 686-0220
